{
    "id": "60c6bc74faf5484599302fa3e999f07e",
    "title": "Word Formation Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have known each other since our ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "childhood",
                "childlike",
                "childish"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29bb632ce8dc47adaec574c904f8b01d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His hard work ……………………. him to pass his examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "able",
                "enable",
                "abled",
                "enabled"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2e6c1bbcf236482aa28f9a8ac423c721"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager asked the board members to ………………….. his earlier proposal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reconsider",
                "consideration",
                "considerable"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db1e4672bb9049a2882d81109487ec6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only a fool will …………………… his net worth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "estimate",
                "underestimate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aee254fa6b8495dab600debaf2ea47e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a stupid and often talks ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sense",
                "sensible",
                "nonsense"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0959eec5ca2348c8a39584ec6b018ac2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Government of China has ………………….. its currency.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "valued",
                "valuable",
                "devalued"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04a11e38a8f14c93823c3968cea5f4ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Parents should not ………………… their children’s mistakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look",
                "look over",
                "overlook"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e1fdc51fb504320bc949531de85a04c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was absent because he was …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "unwell",
                "wellness"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59a71df2c00f4d689fed15e87ba6dd22"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judgment ……………………. in our favor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9baa7673635f42498e6b5bf2a01c657c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge ordered that the accused be ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "behead",
                "beheading",
                "beheaded"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96741320021844b8960f0ceedc6d9975"
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister wants to …………………….. the capital.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beauty",
                "beautify",
                "beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ade28e270bc34ea78ef4981d28bc8022"
        }
    ]
}